Guide to the Sports Information Office Records, 1932-ongoing UA.13.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- UA2013-0034, 1927-2015
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson; Duke vs. North Carolina, January 26, 2006; January 29, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech; Duke vs. Virginia, February 6, 2006; February 10, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. Miami, February 13, 2006; February 19, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech; Duke vs. North Carolina, February 22, 2006; February 25, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.110)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Tournament, 2006-03-04 (Box UA2013-0034.110)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Media Supplement, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.110)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament, 2006-04-04 (Box UA2013-0034.110)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. Georgia Tech, January 8, 2006; January 11, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.110)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College; Duke vs. Holy Cross, January 14, 2006; January 16, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.110)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament, 2006-04-02 (Box UA2013-0034.110)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament, 2006-03-28 (Box UA2013-0034.110)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament, 2006-03-19 (Box UA2013-0034.110)
  - Women's Basketball: Scorebook and Media Guide, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Rankings/Polls, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Scouting Information, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Team Information, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Notes, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Information, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Press Releases, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Clippings, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke Blue vs. Duke White; Duke vs. EA Sports Exhibition; Duke vs. Denver University, October 28, 2007; November 8, 2007; November 11, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. South Florida; Duke vs. UNC Greensboro; Duke vs. Purdue, November 15, 2007; November 18, 2007; November 22, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Penn State; Duke vs. Rutgers; Duke vs. Pittsburgh, December 2, 2007; December 6, 2007; December 8, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Utah Valley; Duke vs. Bucknell; Duke vs. Houston, December 18, 2007; December 21, 2007; December 28, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. NC Central; Duke vs. Miami; Duke vs. Florida State, January 3, 2008; January 5, 2008; January 11, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Temple; Duke vs. Connecticut; Duke vs. Vanderbilt, November 23, 2007; November 25, 2007; November 28, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.112)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. NC State; Duke vs. Georgia Tech, January 14, 2008; January 20, 2008; January 24, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.112)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Tennessee; Duke vs. Virginia Tech; Duke vs. North Carolina, January 28, 2008; February 1, 2008; February 4, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.112)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College; Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. Clemson, February 7, 2008; February 10, 2008; February 13, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.112)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2008-03-02 (Box UA2013-0034.112)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. Virginia Tech; Duke vs. Virginia, February 17, 2008; February 22, 2008; February 24, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.112)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Round 1 and 2, March 23, 2008; March 25, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.112)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Sweet Sixteen, 2008-03-30 (Box UA2013-0034.112)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Media Guides, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.112)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Siena, 2008-12-20 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Quinnipiac, 2008-12-28 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Michigan, 2008-12-07 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Stanford, 2008-12-16 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Western Kentucky, 2008-11-28 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Iowa, 2008-12-04 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Oklahoma State; Duke vs. Maine, November 14, 2008; November 16, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Hartford; Duke vs. Southern, November 21-22, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Media Guides, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Polls, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Releases, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Notes, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Box Scores, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Photos, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke Blue White Scrimmage; Duke vs. Anderson, October 26, 2008; November 6, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Tournament, March 7-9, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Media Supplement, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State University; Duke vs. Maryland, March 7-March 8, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Austin Peay; Duke vs. Michigan State University, March 22, 2009; March 24, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina; Duke vs. Virginia, March 1, 2009; March 6, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Tennessee; Duke vs. Virginia Tech, February 16, 2009; February 19, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina; Duke vs. Clemson, February 9, 2009; February 13, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College; Duke vs. Virginia, February 2, 2009; February 5, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State, 2009-01-29 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2009-01-16 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State; Duke vs. Georgia Tech, January 19, 2009; January 25, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2009-01-12 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami, 2009-01-09 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Temple, 2009-01-05 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Providence, 2009-12-31 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Photos, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia, 2010-02-26 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2010-02-28 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. NC Central, 2009-12-28 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Temple, 2009-12-31 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Providence, 2010-01-03 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson, 2010-01-07 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2010-01-10 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami, 2010-01-14 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Connecticut, 2010-01-18 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2010-01-21 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2010-01-24 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State, 2010-01-29 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College, 2010-02-04 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2010-02-08 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State, 2010-02-11 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2010-02-14 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2010-02-19 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2010-02-21 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Temple, 2010-12-30 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Kentucky, 2011-01-04 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2011-01-06 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State, 2011-01-14 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2011-01-16 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Albany, 2010-12-09 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Oklahoma State, 2010-12-12 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Xavier, 2010-12-21 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. James Madison, 2010-11-30 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wisconsin, 2010-12-02 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Texas A&M, 2010-12-06 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Auburn, 2010-11-18 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Western Kentucky, 2010-11-21 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Pittsburgh, 2010-11-24 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Charlotte, 2010-11-27 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. BYU, 2010-11-13 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs Miami, 2011-02-03 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2011-02-07 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2011-01-21 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State, 2011-01-23 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson, 2011-01-26 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Southern California, 2010-11-15 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Blue White Scrimmage Exhibition, circa 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2011-02-27 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College, 2011-02-13 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2011-02-17 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2011-02-20 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Celebration Program, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Connecticut, 2011-01-31 (Box UA2013-0034.117)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament, March 21, 2011; March 27, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.117)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia, 2011-02-24 (Box UA2013-0034.117)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2011-02-11 (Box UA2013-0034.117)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament, March 19, 2011; March 21, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.117)
  - Women's Basketball: ACC Tournament, March 4-6, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.117)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2011-03-11 (Box UA2013-0034.117)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2011-03-12 (Box UA2013-0034.117)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2011-03-13 (Box UA2013-0034.117)
  - Player Files Ab-Al, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.117)
  - Player Files Al-Ay, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.118)
  - Player Files Ay-Ba, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.119)
  - Player Files Ba-Be, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.120)
  - Player Files Be-Be, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.121)
  - Player Files Be-Bl, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.122)
  - Player Files Bl-Bo, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.123)
  - Player Files Bo-Br, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.124)
  - Player Files Br-Bu, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.125)
  - Player Files Bu-Bu, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.126)
  - Player Files Ca-Ca, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.127)
  - Player Files Ca-Ch, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.128)
  - Player Files Ch-Cl, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.129)
  - Player Files Cl-Co, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.130)
  - Player Files Co-Cu, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.131)
  - Player Files Cu-Da, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.132)
  - Player Files Da-Da, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.133)
  - Player Files Da-Di, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.134)
  - Player Files Di-Du, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.135)
  - Player Files Du-Dy, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.136)
  - Player Files Ea-Fa, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.137)
  - Player Files Fa-Fi, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.138)
  - Player Files Fi-Fo, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.139)
  - Player Files Fr-Ga, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.140)
  - Player Files Ga-Go, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.141)
  - Player Files Go-Gr, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.142)
  - Player Files Gr-Ha, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.143)
  - Player Files Ha-Ha, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.144)
  - Player Files Ha-He, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.145)
  - Player Files He-Hi, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.146)
  - Player Files Hi-Ho, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.147)
  - Player Files Ho-Hu, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.148)
  - Player Files Hu-Ja, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.149)
  - Player Files Ja-Jo, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.150)
  - Player Files Jo-Ke, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.151)
  - Player Files Ke-Ko, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.152)
  - Player Files Ko-La, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.153)
  - Player Files La-La, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.154)
  - Player Files La-Li, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.155)
  - Player Files Li-Ma, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.156)
  - Player Files Ma-Ma, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.157)
  - Player Files Ma-Mc, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.158)
  - Player Files Mc-Mc, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.159)
  - Player Files Mc-Mi, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.160)
  - Player Files Mi-Mo, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.161)
  - Player Files Mo-Ne, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.162)
  - Player Files Ne-No, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.163)
  - Player Files No-Pa, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.164)
  - Player Files Pa-Pa, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.165)
  - Player Files Pa-Pl, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.166)
  - Player Files Pl-Ra, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.167)
  - Player Files Ra-Re, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.168)
  - Player Files Re-Ro, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.169)
  - Player Files Ro-Sa, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.170)
  - Player Files Sa-Sc, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.171)
  - Player Files Sc-Si, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.172)
  - Player Files Si-Sm, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.173)
  - Player Files Sm-So, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.174)
  - Player Files So-St, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.175)
  - Player Files St-Te, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.176)
  - Player Files Te-To, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.177)
  - Player Files To-Va, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.178)
  - Player Files Va-Wa, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.179)
  - Player Files Wa-Wa, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.180)
  - Player Files Wa-We, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.181)
  - Player Files We-Wi, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.182)
  - Player Files Wi-Wi, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.183)
  - Player Files Wi-Wy, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.184)
  - Player Files Ya-Za, circa 1979-2015 (Box UA2013-0034.185)
  - Basketball Office, circa 2009-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.185)
  - Training Staff, circa 2009-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.185)
  - Basketball: Press Releases, circa 2009-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.185)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets, 1997 (Box UA2013-0034.185)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1998-1999 (Box UA2013-0034.185)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets, 1999 (Box UA2013-0034.185)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1999-2000 (Box UA2013-0034.185)
  - Men's Basketball: Miscellaneous, circa 1997-1999; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.185)
  - Football: Slides, 1970-1999; 8 folders (Box UA2013-0034.186)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1981-1982 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1980-1981 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1979-1980 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1978-1979 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1971-1972 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1972-1973 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1973-1975 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1976-1977 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1977-1978 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1938-1960 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1962-1963 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1963-1964 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1965-1967 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1967-1968 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1969-1970 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1982-1983 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1984-1985 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1984-1985 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
    Includes photographic prints and negatives.
  - Football: Team Photos, 1985 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Team Photos, 1986 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos and Contact Sheets, 1985-1986 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Promotions, 1987-1988 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1986-1987 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1987-1988 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos and Composite Sheets, 1988-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photo Book, circa 1984-1994 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1992-1993 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets, 1993 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets, 1994 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1993-1994 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets, 1993-1994 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1994-1995 (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1997-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.188)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets, 1998 (Box UA2013-0034.188)
  - Men's Basketball: Composites; Headshots, 1996-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.188)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets, 1996 (Box UA2013-0034.188)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets, 1995-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.188)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets, 1995 (Box UA2013-0034.188)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, September-November 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.188)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.188)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, April-August 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.188)
  - Men's Basketball: Mike Krzyzewski, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.188)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. St. Augustine's, 2010-10-23 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Countdown to Craziness, 2010-10-15 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Cal Poly Pomona, 2010-11-04 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Princeton, 2010-11-14 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami OH, 2010-11-16 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Colgate, 2010-11-19 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Marquette, 2010-11-22 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Kansas State, 2010-11-23 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Oregon, 2010-11-27 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Michigan State, 2010-12-01 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Butler, 2010-12-04 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Bradley, 2010-12-08 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. St. Louis, 2010-12-11 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Elon, 2010-12-20 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. UNC Greensboro, 2010-12-29 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami, 2011-01-02 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Alabama-Birmingham, 2011-01-05 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2011-01-09 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State, 2011-01-12 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia, 2011-01-15 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State, 2011-01-19 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2011-01-22 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College, 2011-01-27 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. St. John's, 2011-01-30 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2011-02-02 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State, 2011-02-05 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2011-02-09 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami, 2011-02-13 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia, 2011-02-16 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2011-02-20 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Temple, 2011-02-23 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2011-02-26 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson, 2011-03-02 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2011-03-05 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, circa 2009-2013; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2010-02-04 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College, 2010-02-06 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2010-02-10 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2010-02-13 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami, 2010-02-17 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2010-02-21 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Tulsa, 2010-02-25 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia, 2010-02-28 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2010-03-03 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2010-03-06 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia, 2010-03-12 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami, 2010-03-13 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2010-03-14 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Arkansas-Pine Bluff, 2010-03-19 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. California, 2010-03-21 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Purdue, 2010-03-26 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. West Virginia, 2010-04-03 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Baylor, 2010-03-28 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Butler, 2010-04-05 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2012-01-19 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State, 2012-01-21 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2012-01-25 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. St. John's, 2012-01-28 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2012-02-02 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami, 2012-02-05 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2012-02-08 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2012-02-11 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State, 2012-02-16 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College, 2012-02-19 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State, 2012-02-23 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2012-02-25 (Box UA2013-0034.193)